Register of the John Davis Lodge papers, 1886-1987
Hoover Institution Archives
- U.S. Congress (1946-1950) File, 1945-1950 (Boxes 15-30)
  - Biographical file, 1946-1950, undated
    - Campaign, 1948
      - Speeches (Box-folder 17: 4)
      - Statistical analysis (Box-folder 17: 5-6)
      - Young Voter's Club (Box-folder 17: 7)
    - Clippings, 1946-1950 (Box-folder 17: 8-11, 18: 1-8)
    - Memberships/clubs (Box-folder 18: 9)
  - Correspondence, 1945-1950
    - General
      - Unidentified, 1946-1950 (Box-folder 18: 10)
      - 1945 (Box-folder 18: 11)
      - 1946 (Box-folder 19: 1-9)
      - 1947 (Box-folder 20: 1-2)
      - 1948 (Box-folder 20: 3-4)
      - 1949 (Box-folder 20: 5)
      - 1950 (Box-folder 20: 6)
    - Adorno, Joseph A., 1946 (Box-folder 20: 7)
    - Ainley, Mrs. Henry, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 20: 8)
    - Aldrich, Richard S., 1946-1948 (Box-folder 20: 9)
    - Allen, Edward, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 20: 10)
    - American Economic Foundation, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 20: 11)
    - American Legion Post, 1946 (Box-folder 20: 12)
    - American Magazine, 1947 (Box-folder 20: 13)
    - American Speakers and Writers Bureau, 1946 (Box-folder 20: 14)
    - Baldwin, Raymond E., 1946 (Box-folder 20: 15)
    - Banks, Polan, 1946 (Box-folder 20: 16)
    - Benton, William, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 20: 17)
    - Bohlen, Charles, 1948 (Box-folder 20: 18)
    - Boit, Julian, 1946 (Box-folder 20: 19)
    - Bolton-Smith, Carlile, 1947 (Box-folder 20: 20)
    - Bradley, Kenneth, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 20: 21)
    - Braggiotti, D. Chadwick, 1946 (Box-folder 20: 22)
    - Braggiotti, Mario, 1946 (Box-folder 20: 23)
    - Braggiotti, Sebastiano, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 20: 24)
    - Brennan, William H., 1946-1948 (Box-folder 20: 25)
    - Brown, John Mason, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 20: 26)
    - Bush, Prescott, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 20: 27)
    - Burns, Ward R., 1946 (Box-folder 20: 28)
    - Butler and Baldwin, 1946 (Box-folder 20: 29)
    - Carlson, Theodore, 1946 (Box-folder 20: 30)
    - Casey, John T., 1946 (Box-folder 20: 31)
    - Cassedy, Anthony, 1946 (Box-folder 20: 32)
    - Chase, Allan, 1946 (Box-folder 20: 33)
    - Clark, Fred, 1946 (Box-folder 20: 34)
    - Cogan, Bernard, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 20: 35)
    - Colgate, Bayard, 1948 (Box-folder 20: 36)
    - Coudert, Frederic, Jr., 1946 (Box-folder 20: 37)
    - Cowles, Gardner, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 20: 38)
    - Crocker, Edward S., 1946 (Box-folder 20: 39)
    - Cunningham, Edward, 1948 (Box-folder 20: 40)
    - Cutler, Robert, 1946 (Box-folder 20: 41)
    - Dainelli, Luca, 1947 (Box-folder 20: 42)
    - Davis, Elizabeth, 1948 (Box-folder 21: 1)
    - Denfeld, Louis, 1948 (Box-folder 21: 2)
    - Dewart, Thomas G., 1946-1949 (Box-folder 21: 3)
    - Dewey, Thomas E., 1948 (Box-folder 21: 4)
    - Dirksen, Everett, 1948 (Box-folder 21: 5)
    - Dohanos, Steven, 1946 (Box-folder 21: 6)
    - Doyle, Ted, 1946 (Box-folder 21: 7)
    - Drouin, Dominique, 1946 (Box-folder 21: 8)
    - Duffy, Charles, 1946 (Box-folder 21: 9)
    - Eames, Hamilton, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 21: 10)
    - Eaton, Charles, 1948 (Box-folder 21: 11)
    - Etting, Emlen, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 21: 12)
    - Fairbanks, Douglas, Jr., 1946 (Box-folder 21: 13)
    - Faulker, Worthe, 1946 (Box-folder 21: 14)
    - Ferne, Henry, II, 1946 (Box-folder 21: 15)
    - Forrestal, James, 1946 (Box-folder 21: 16)
    - Francoeur, Philip, 1946 (Box-folder 21: 17)
    - Frelinghuysen, Matilda, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 21: 18)
    - Fuller, Alfred C., 1946-1948 (Box-folder 21: 19)
    - Fuller, Margaret, 1950 (Box-folder 21: 20)
    - Grimes, Charles, 1948 (Box-folder 21: 21)
    - Harlow, Brooks, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 21: 22)
    - Hart, Thomas, 1946 (Box-folder 21: 23)
    - Harvard Club, 1946 (Box-folder 21: 24)
    - Hayes, Henry, 1948 (Box-folder 21: 25)
    - Hewitt, Henry K., 1946 (Box-folder 21: 26)
    - Hillenkoetter, R. H., 1948 (Box-folder 21: 27)
    - Hulick, C. V., 1948 (Box-folder 21: 28)
    - Ives, Colin C., 1946-1948 (Box-folder 21: 29)
    - Jackson, Donald, 1948 (Box-folder 21: 30)
    - Jacques, Henriette, 1946 (Box-folder 21: 31)
    - Javits, Jacob, 1948 (Box-folder 21: 32)
    - Jessup, Mrs. H. H., 1946 (Box-folder 21: 33)
    - Johnson, Mrs. Willard, 1946 (Box-folder 21: 34)
    - Kiely, Thomas B., 1946 (Box-folder 21: 35)
    - Lamont, Betty, 1947-1950 (Box-folder 21: 36)
    - Langner, Lawrence, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 21: 37)
    - League of Women Voters, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 21: 38)
    - Lebedeff, Ivan, 1946-1949 (Box-folder 21: 39)
    - Lemnitzer, L. L., 1949 (Box-folder 21: 40)
    - Lodge, Francesca, 1947 (Box-folder 21: 41)
    - Lodge, Henry C., Jr., 1946 (Box-folder 21: 42)
    - Lodge, Mrs. John Ellerton, 1946 (Box-folder 21: 43)
    - Lodge, Lily, 1948 (Box-folder 21: 44)
    - Lodge, Mathilda Elizabeth, 1946 (Box-folder 21: 45)
    - Luce, Clare Boothe, 1946 (Box-folder 21: 46)
    - MacArthur, Douglas, II, 1948 (Box-folder 21: 47)
    - Martin, Joseph W., Jr., 1946-1948 (Box-folder 21: 48)
    - Meek, Samuel, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 21: 49)
    - Mentz, Admiral Francis, 1947 (Box-folder 21: 50)
    - Minot, William, 1948 (Box-folder 21: 51)
    - Montgomery, Douglass, 1948 (Box-folder 21: 52)
    - Mumford, George, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 21: 53)
    - Neusner, Samuel, 1950 (Box-folder 21: 54)
    - Noel, Sterling, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 21: 55)
    - Norwalk Jewish Community Center, 1947 (Box-folder 21: 56)
    - Ogden, Robert, 1946 (Box-folder 21: 57)
    - Ophuls, Max, 1946 (Box-folder 21: 58)
    - Paget, Reginald Thomas, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 21: 59)
    - Patterson, James T., 1949 (Box-folder 21: 60)
    - Peterson, Oscar, 1946 (Box-folder 21: 61)
    - Pound, Roscoe, 1946 (Box-folder 22: 1)
    - Pryor, Samuel, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 22: 2)
    - Pujo, Madelaine, 1946 (Box-folder 22: 3)
    - Rabb, Maxwell, 1946 (Box-folder 22: 4)
    - Redmond, Charles, 1946 (Box-folder 22: 5)
    - Remington Rand, 1946 (Box-folder 22: 6)
    - Republican National Committee, 1946 (Box-folder 22: 7)
    - Republican State Central Committee, 1946 (Box-folder 22: 8)
    - Rimanoczy, R. S., 1946 (Box-folder 22: 9)
    - Rogers, Alan Stewart, 1946 (Box-folder 22: 10)
    - Routh, Robert, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 22: 11)
    - Shannon, James, 1948 (Box-folder 22: 12)
    - Sinon, Frank, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 22: 13)
    - Smith, Truman, 1946 (Box-folder 22: 14)
    - Sokolsky, George, 1946 (Box-folder 22: 15)
    - Spear, Jackson, 1946 (Box-folder 22: 16)
    - Stassen, Harold, 1946 (Box-folder 22: 17)
    - Steele, Bernard, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 22: 18)
    - Stoddart, Dayton, 1946 (Box-folder 22: 19)
    - Straus, Roger, Jr., 1946 (Box-folder 22: 20)
    - Streel, Helena Lodge de, 1946 (Box-folder 22: 21)
    - Sunday Herald, 1946 (Box-folder 22: 22)
    - Thaw, Lawrence, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 22: 23)
    - Tomlin, Jean, 1948 (Box-folder 22: 24)
    - Tool Owners Union, 1946 (Box-folder 22: 25)
    - Truman, Harry, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 22: 26)
    - Tynan, Olive, 1946 (Box-folder 22: 27)
    - Walther, Max, 1946 (Box-folder 22: 28)
    - Watson, Lucille, 1946 (Box-folder 22: 29)
    - Watt, Raymond, 1946-1950 (Box-folder 22: 30)
    - Weiss, Gaspard, 1948 (Box-folder 22: 31)
    - Williams, Mrs. C. C., 1946-1948 (Box-folder 22: 32)
    - Williams, Paul, 1946 (Box-folder 22: 33)
    - Wood, John, 1946 (Box-folder 22: 34)
    - Yacopino, John, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 22: 35)
    - Zeller, Fred, 1946 (Box-folder 22: 36)
  - Office file, 1947-1949, undated
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 22: 37)
    - Committees
      - Foreign Affairs (Box-folder 22: 38)
      - Judiciary (Box-folder 22: 39)
    - Legislation, general (Box-folder 22: 40, 23: 1)
    - Organization chart, executive branch (Box-folder 23: 2)
    - Press releases, Republican State Central Committee (Box-folder 23: 3)
    - Reports
      - Aid to Italy
        - General (Box-folder 23: 4)
        - Correspondence (Box-folder 23: 5)
        - Legislation (Box-folder 23: 6)
        - Memoranda (Box-folder 23: 7)
        - Press releases (Box-folder 23: 8)
        - Reports (Box-folder 23: 9)
      - Chance-Vought Company (Box-folder 23: 10)
      - Espionage on atomic research and development (Box-folder 23: 11)
      - Katyn Massacre (Box-folder 23: 12)
      - Korean Aid Bill (Box-folder 23: 13)
      - Poland and Polish immigration (Box-folder 23: 14)
      - Trade with the U.S.S.R. (Box-folder 23: 15)
      - U.S. Information Program in Italy (Box-folder 24: 1)
    - Research files, list (Box-folder 24: 2)
    - Travel file
      - Europe, 1947-1949 (Box-folder 24: 3-4)
      - Belgium (Box-folder 24: 5)
      - London (Box-folder 24: 6)
    - Voting records
      - General (Box-folder 24: 7)
      - Benton, William (Box-folder 24: 8)
      - Byrnes, John (Box-folder 24: 9)
      - Lodge, John Davis (Box-folder 24: 10)
      - Ribicoff, A. A. (Box-folder 24: 11)
      - Woodhouse, Chase (Box-folder 24: 12)
  - Speeches and writings, 1946-1950
    - Index (Box-folder 24: 13)
    - Drafts, holograph notes, undated (Box-folder 24: 14)
    - Speeches, undated (Box-folder 24: 15)
    - 1946 (Box-folder 24: 16-18)
      Includes research materials.
    - 1947 (Box-folder 24: 19, 25: 1-4)
      Includes U.S. Congress monthly reports and remarks.
    - 1948 (Box-folder 25: 5-7, 26: 1-4)
    - 1949 (Box-folder 26: 5-8, 27: 1-4)
      Includes partial draft of an autobiography, research materials, and U.S. Congress monthly reports and remarks.
    - 1950 (Box-folder 27: 5-7, 28: 1-2)
      Includes research materials and U.S. Congress monthly reports and remarks.
  - Subject file, 1946-1949, undated
    - Acheson, Dean, undated (Box-folder 28: 3)
      Julius Epstein, "The Case Against Dean Acheson," mimeographed copy.
    - Automobiles in the U.S., circa 1948 (Box-folder 28: 4)
      Typescript survey.
    - Barnum, P.T. (Box-folder 28: 5)
    - Burke, Edmund (Box-folder 28: 6)
    - China, economic assistance program, 1948 (Box-folder 28: 7)
    - Clark, Fred G., undated (Box-folder 28: 8)
      "Wake Up, America", printed copies.
    - Clay, Lucius (Box-folder 28: 9)
    - Communist Party (Box-folder 28: 10)
    - Connecticut (Box-folder 28: 11)
    - Connecticut Petroleum Industries Committee (Box-folder 28: 12)
    - Dentistry (Box-folder 28: 13)
    - Dewey, Thomas E. (Box-folder 28: 14-15)
    - Economic assistance (Box-folder 28: 16-17)
      Reports and statements.
    - Economic conditions (Box-folder 29: 1)
    - Foreign relations, 1946 (Box-folder 29: 2)
      Henry Cabot Lodge, Jr., "The Citizen and Foreign Policy," typescript.
    - French-American Club (Box-folder 29: 3)
    - Germany (Box-folder 29: 4)
    - Hungary (Box-folder 29: 5)
    - Italy (Box-folder 29: 6)
    - Labor (Box-folder 29: 7)
    - Lodge, Henry Cabot, Jr. (Box-folder 29: 8)
      Speeches, writings, and excerpts from his public office record.
    - Malaxa, Nicolae (Box-folder 29: 9)
      Memoirs, typescript.
    - Marshall, George C. (Box-folder 29: 10)
    - Miscellany (Box-folder 29: 11)
    - Palermo Boys Home (Box-folder 30: 1)
    - Poland (Box-folder 30: 2)
    - Politics and government (Box-folder 30: 3)
    - Polls, 1948 (Box-folder 30: 4)
      George Gallup, "Accuracy of Modern Polling Techniques in Making Election Forecasts," printed copy.
    - Republican Party
      - Republican National Committee, undated (Box-folder 30: 5)
        "Inflation... and How to Beat It," printed copy.
      - Robert W. Taylor, "Republican Glide," printed copy, undated (Box-folder 30: 6)
    - Spain (Box-folder 30: 7)
    - Stassen, Harold, 1948 September 7 (Box-folder 30: 8)
      Speech, typescript.
    - Stevenson, Suzanne (Box-folder 30: 9)
    - Taft, Robert A., 1948 September 23 (Box-folder 30: 10)
    - Truman, Harry S. (Box-folder 30: 11)
    - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics (U.S.S.R.) (Box-folder 30: 12)
    - United Nations (Box-folder 30: 13)
    - United States Congress
      - House of Representatives, 1949 October 23 (Box-folder 30: 14)
        Committee on Un-American Activities, "Report on the Congress of American Women," printed copy.
      - House bills (Box-folder 30: 15)
      - Voting records (Box-folder 30: 16)
    - Vigilantes (Box-folder 30: 17)
    - Warren, Earl (Box-folder 30: 18)
    - Westport Harbor and Saugatuck River (Box-folder 30: 19)
    - Yokohama (Box-folder 30: 20)
- Governor of Connecticut (1950-1954) File, 1939-1955 (Boxes 30-84)
  Biographical material (including Lodge's re-election campaign), correspondence, office materials, speeches and writings, and general subject material.
  - Biographical file, 1950-1955, undated
    - Admission to Connecticut Bar (Box-folder 30: 21)
    - Appointment calendars (Box-folder 30: 22)
    - Awards, citations (Box-folder 30: 23)
    - Biographical data (Box-folder 30: 24)
    - Campaign, 1950
      - General
        - Clippings (Box-folder 30: 25-26)
        - Correspondence (Box-folder 30: 27)
        - Finances (Box-folder 30: 28)
        - Issues (Box-folder 31: 1-3)
        - Literature (Box-folder 31: 4-5)
        - Memoranda (Box-folder 31: 6)
        - Opponents (Box-folder 31: 7)
        - Platform (Box-folder 31: 8)
        - Schedule (Box-folder 31: 9)
      - Acceptance of nomination (Box-folder 31: 10)
      - Americans for Democratic Action (Box-folder 31: 11)
      - Classmates for Lodge Committee (Box-folder 32: 1)
      - Clubs (Box-folder 32: 2)
      - Committee of Two Thousand for Lodge (Box-folder 32: 3)
      - Committee on Un-American Activities (Box-folder 32: 4)
      - Connecticut officals (Box-folder 32: 5)
      - Democratic National Committee (Box-folder 32: 6)
      - League of Women Voters (Box-folder 32: 7)
      - Lodge for Governor Committee (Box-folder 32: 8)
      - Miscellany (Box-folder 32: 9)
      - News media (Box-folder 32: 10)
      - Press releases, statements (Box-folder 32: 11)
      - Republican Party (Box-folder 32: 12)
      - Republican State Central Committee (Box-folder 32: 13)
      - Research materials (Box-folder 32: 14)
      - Statistics (Box-folder 33: 1)
      - Strategy and planning (Box-folder 33: 2)
      - Voting records (Box-folder 33: 3)
    - Campaign, 1954
      - General
        - Clippings (Box-folder 33: 4)
        - Correspondence (Box-folder 33: 5)
        - Literature (Box-folder 33: 6)
        - Memoranda (Box-folder 33: 7)
        - Staff (Box-folder 33: 8)
      - Citizens for Lodge (Box-folder 33: 9)
      - Public opinion poll (Box-folder 33: 10)
      - Reports on the Lodge Administration (Box-folder 33: 11)
      - Republican Party handbook (Box-folder 33: 12)
      - Republican State Central Committee (Box-folder 33: 13)
    - Clippings, 1950-1955 (Box-folder 33: 14 - 52: 9)
    - Harvard Class reunion, 1950 (Box-folder 52: 10)
    - Lecture Bureau (Box-folder 52: 11)
    - Memberships/clubs (Box-folder 52: 12)
    - Miscellany (Box-folder 52: 13)
    - Naval Reserve (Box-folder 53: 1)
    - Passport information (Box-folder 53: 2)
    - Security clearance (Box-folder 53: 3)
    - Travel
      - Hawaii, 1953 (Box-folder 53: 4)
      - Italy, 1954 (Box-folder 53: 5)
  - Correspondence, 1950-1955
    - General
      - 1950 (Box-folder 53: 6 - 56: 2)
      - 1951 (Box-folder 56: 3-5)
      - 1952 (Box-folder 56: 6-9, 57: 1-3)
      - 1953 (Box-folder 57: 4-8, 58: 1-3)
      - 1954 (Box-folder 58: 4 - 61: 7)
      - 1955 (Box-folder 61: 8)
    - Adams, Sherman, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 61: 9)
    - Ainley, Elaine, 1951-1954 (Box-folder 62: 1)
    - Alcorn, H. Meade, Jr., 1952-1954 (Box-folder 62: 2)
    - Aldrich, Richard S., 1950-1954 (Box-folder 62: 3)
    - Allen, Edward, 1951-1954 (Box-folder 62: 4)
    - Alsop, Corinne, 1952-1954 (Box-folder 62: 5)
    - Alsop, John, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 62: 6)
    - Anders, Wladyslaw, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 62: 7)
    - Aumont, Jean Pierre, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 62: 8)
    - Ballentine, John, 1953 (Box-folder 62: 9)
    - Banks, Polan, 1951-1954 (Box-folder 62: 10)
    - Barrymore, Ethel, 1954 (Box-folder 62: 11)
    - Benoit, Pierre, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 62: 12)
    - Benton, William, 1954 (Box-folder 62: 13)
    - Bobich, Gica, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 62: 14)
    - Bolton-Smith, Carlile, 1951-1954 (Box-folder 62: 15)
    - Bowles, Chester, 1952 (Box-folder 62: 16)
    - Bradford, Robert, 1951-1954 (Box-folder 62: 17)
    - Braggiotti, D. Chadwick, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 62: 18)
    - Braggiotti, Francine, 1954 (Box-folder 62: 19)
    - Braggiotti, Frank, 1954 (Box-folder 62: 20)
    - Braggiotti, Mario, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 62: 21)
    - Braggiotti, Mary, 1954 (Box-folder 62: 22)
    - Braggiotti, Rama, 1952-1954 (Box-folder 62: 23)
    - Brown, John Mason, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 62: 24)
    - Brunner, Carl, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 62: 25)
    - Bush, Prescott, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 62: 26)
    - Byrnes, James F., 1953 (Box-folder 62: 27)
    - Carroll-Abbing, John, 1952-1954 (Box-folder 62: 28)
    - Casey, John T., 1950-1954 (Box-folder 62: 29)
    - Chapius, Jeanne, 1952-1954 (Box-folder 62: 30)
    - Clark, Edward, 1952-1954 (Box-folder 62: 31)
    - Clay, Lucius, 1952 (Box-folder 62: 32)
    - Cogan, Bernard, 1950-1953 (Box-folder 62: 33)
    - Cole, Albert, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 62: 34)
    - Colgate, Bayard, 1952 (Box-folder 62: 35)
    - Cooper, Lowell, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 62: 36)
    - Coote, Al, 1950-1953 (Box-folder 62: 37)
    - Costarelli, Emilie, 1952 (Box-folder 62: 38)
    - Cousins, Norman, 1952 (Box-folder 62: 39)
    - Cowles, Gardner, 1951-1954 (Box-folder 62: 40)
    - Crittenberger, Willis, 1952 (Box-folder 63: 1)
    - Crocker, Lispenard, 1952-1954 (Box-folder 63: 2)
    - Cunningham, Mrs. Edward, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 63: 3)
    - Cutler, Robert, 1950-1953 (Box-folder 63: 4)
    - Danaher, John A., 1952-1954 (Box-folder 63: 5)
    - Davidson, Sarita, 1954 (Box-folder 63: 6)
    - Davis, Elizabeth, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 63: 7)
    - DeCastro, Morris, 1952 (Box-folder 63: 8)
    - Dewart, Thomas G., 1951-1954 (Box-folder 63: 9)
    - Dewey, Thomas E., 1950-1954 (Box-folder 63: 10)
    - Dirksen, Everett, 1950 (Box-folder 63: 11)
    - Dohanos, Stevan, 1954 (Box-folder 63: 12)
    - Downey, Morton, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 63: 13)
    - Drouin, Dominique, 1951-1954 (Box-folder 63: 14)
    - Dulles, Allen, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 63: 15)
    - Dulles, John Foster, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 63: 16)
    - Eames, Emma, 1952 (Box-folder 63: 17)
    - Eames, Hamilton, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 63: 18-19)
    - Earl, N.C., 1950-1954 (Box-folder 63: 20)
    - Eaton, Charles A., 1951-1953 (Box-folder 63: 21)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1952-1954 (Box-folder 63: 22)
    - Emerson, Willard, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 63: 23)
    - Esquivel, Mario, 1954 (Box-folder 63: 24)
    - Etting, Emlen, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 63: 25)
    - Fairbanks, Douglas, Jr., 1950-1952 (Box-folder 63: 26)
    - Faulkner, Worthe, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 63: 27)
    - Ferne, Henry, II, 1952-1954 (Box-folder 63: 28)
    - Figueros, Jose, 1954 (Box-folder 63: 29)
    - Freedman, Zac, 1954 (Box-folder 63: 30)
    - Frelinghuysen, Matilda, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 63: 31)
    - Frelinghuysen, Peter, Jr., 1952 (Box-folder 63: 32)
    - Gardner, Hy, 1953 (Box-folder 64: 1)
    - Garraty, John A., 1954 (Box-folder 64: 2)
    - Gasperi, Alcide de, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 64: 3)
    - Gaxton, William, 1952-1954 (Box-folder 64: 4)
    - Goldsmith, Harold, 1952-1954 (Box-folder 64: 5)
    - Goldwater, Barry, 1952 (Box-folder 64: 6)
    - Gould, Samuel, 1950 (Box-folder 64: 7)
    - Grimes, Charles, 1952 (Box-folder 64: 8)
    - Hagerty, James C., 1953 (Box-folder 64: 9)
    - Hall, Leonard, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 64: 10)
    - Harlow, Arthur Brooks, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 64: 11-12)
    - Hart, Thomas, 1951-1954 (Box-folder 64: 13)
    - Harvard University, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 64: 14-15)
    - Hayes, Henry, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 64: 16)
    - Hays, Mortimer, 1950 (Box-folder 64: 17)
    - Herter, Christian, 1952-1954 (Box-folder 64: 18)
    - Hill, G. Albert, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 65: 1)
    - Hill, Robert C., 1954 (Box-folder 65: 2)
    - Hillenkoetter, Roscoe, 1953 (Box-folder 65: 3)
    - Hoover, Herbert, 1954 (Box-folder 65: 4)
    - House, Charles S., 1950-1954 (Box-folder 65: 5)
    - Houston, Howard E., 1954 (Box-folder 65: 6)
    - Humphreys, Rogers, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 65: 7)
    - Hurlburt, Everett, 1954 (Box-folder 65: 8)
    - Ives, Colin C., 1950-1954 (Box-folder 65: 9)
    - Jackson, Donald, 1950-1953 (Box-folder 65: 10)
    - Jarman, Peter, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 65: 11)
    - Javits, Jacob, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 65: 12)
    - Johnson, Mrs. Willard, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 65: 13)
    - Judd, Walter, 1951-1954 (Box-folder 65: 14)
    - Kaufmann, Arthur, 1952-1954 (Box-folder 65: 15)
    - Keats, Charles B., 1954 (Box-folder 65: 16)
    - Kelly, John C., 1950-1954 (Box-folder 65: 17)
    - Kiely, Thomas B., 1954 (Box-folder 65: 18)
    - Lagarde, Jean de, 1951-1954 (Box-folder 65: 19)
    - Lamont, Gordon, 1951-1954 (Box-folder 65: 20-21)
    - Lane, Arthur Bliss, 1950-1952 (Box-folder 65: 22)
    - Langner, Lawrence, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 65: 23)
    - Lebedeff, Ivan, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 65: 24)
    - LePere, Paul, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 65: 25)
    - LePeytre, Henry, 1951-1954 (Box-folder 66: 1)
    - Levy, Herman, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 66: 2)
    - Lewis, Wolfram, 1952 (Box-folder 66: 3)
    - Lodge, Francesca, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 66: 4)
    - Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 66: 5-6)
    - Lodge, John Ellerton, 1954 (Box-folder 66: 7)
    - Lodge, Lily, 1951-1954 (Box-folder 66: 8)
    - Lodge, Mathilda Elizabeth, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 66: 9)
    - Loomis, Patricia, 1951-1953 (Box-folder 66: 10)
    - Loomis, William F., 1950-1954 (Box-folder 66: 11)
    - Lovett, Robert A., 1951 (Box-folder 66: 12)
    - Luce, Clare Boothe, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 66: 13)
    - Luce, Henry, 1952-1954 (Box-folder 66: 14)
    - Lupton, John Mather, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 66: 15)
    - McCarthy, Joseph, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 66: 16)
    - MacKinnon, George E., 1950-1953 (Box-folder 66: 17)
    - Meek, Samuel, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 66: 18)
    - Melton, James, 1951-1953 (Box-folder 66: 19)
    - Mentz, Admiral G. F. M., 1953 (Box-folder 66: 20)
    - Miceli, Riccardo di, 1951-1954 (Box-folder 67: 1)
    - Minot, William A. G., 1952-1955 (Box-folder 67: 2)
    - Montereale, Principe, 1952-1954 (Box-folder 67: 3)
    - Montgomery, Douglass, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 67: 4)
    - Morgan, John Ainsworth, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 67: 5)
    - Mott, Jordan, 1952-1954 (Box-folder 67: 6)
    - Munoz Marin, Luis, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 67: 7)
    - Murphy, George, 1954 (Box-folder 67: 8)
    - Nast, C. Coudert, 1951-1953 (Box-folder 67: 9)
    - Nixon, Richard M., 1950-1954 (Box-folder 67: 10)
    - Noel, Sterling, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 67: 11)
    - O'Brien, Edmund, 1953-1955 (Box-folder 67: 12)
    - Ortona, Egidio, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 67: 13)
    - Palmer, J. Campbell, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 67: 14)
    - Pappas, Thomas, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 67: 15)
    - Parry, Sidney, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 67: 16)
    - Patterson, James T., 1954 (Box-folder 67: 17)
    - Pell, John H. G., 1950-1954 (Box-folder 67: 18)
    - Peterson, Oscar, Jr., 1954 (Box-folder 67: 19)
    - Pickford, Mary, 1952 (Box-folder 67: 20)
    - Pons, Lily, 1954 (Box-folder 67: 21)
    - Pryor, Samuel, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 67: 22)
    - Purtell, William, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 67: 23)
    - Qualls, Floy, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 67: 24)
    - Quinn, James, 1954 (Box-folder 67: 25)
    - Rabb, Maxwell, 1953 (Box-folder 67: 26)
    - Rathbone, Basil, 1953 (Box-folder 67: 27)
    - Reid, Whitelaw, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 67: 28)
    - Reincke, Frederick, 1954 (Box-folder 67: 29)
    - Reynolds, Reginald, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 67: 30)
    - Rogers, Alan, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 67: 31)
    - Rogers, Buddy, 1953 (Box-folder 67: 32)
    - Rogers, Willard, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 67: 33)